Hello friends, whenever we talk to a customer care,
sometimes it happens that
we do not like his way of talking
and at that time we feel
that the customer is talking to us in an unprofessional manner, then
we disconnect the call of the irritated customer,
so for any customer
care executive, it is very important to have an effective phone call because
with its help you
can handle the customer confidently, when you are on a call,
your dressing and looking does
not matter at all,
your effective communication there helps
you, so in this video
I will share with you those used
oil tips, with the help of this you can now
handle the customer easily with confidence,
you can easily convince him,
so do watch this video till the end
and for more such videos
subscribe to our channel and press the bell icon, so
let's start, ah
hello friends, I am Garima, I welcome
you  There are
two types of misuse on our YouTube channel Ghareli Tricks,
one is in-call and the other is on-call.
In these fall outs, the
companies call the customers
for promotion of their services and products or to provide information related to it,
whereas in these calls, the
customers
call the company for the solution of this problem
or for any small problem. The
biggest challenge in this is that
I have to make 200 to 300 calls in a day, from
morning till
evening. All these calls have to be completed,
that too with proper solution.
We have to give proper solution to the customer in minimum time
and he should be
hundred percent satisfied in it. So
finally, when our calls get
connected, then some steps have to be
followed. Now let's talk about them.
Our first step is to make a call.
Friends, you must have heard that first impression
is the last impression. We have to
engage the customer in this process.  The customer should
feel that he is feeling comfortable with us,
we have to give special greetings to the customer in the setting
like good morning sir,
good afternoon sir so that the customer feels good, the
customer should feel that we are giving him
importance, we are giving him respect
and along with that you should tell the customer your name and the
location of the company, what work the company does,
all these things are
discussed in seconds, know your customer, we have to
know about the customer,
where is the customer from, his place, his district
name, his complete biodata is more, what is
his income source,
what is his profession and what is his financial condition, can
he invest in any service or
pro,
so we have to know all this, there is a
little listening to the
customer properly, so when we talk to the customer,
when he tells us any problem,
then we have to listen to his problem completely
and listen carefully, we should
not do such a thing that we interrupt his words.
Or we are
disconnecting the call, the customer should feel that
we are listening to his words carefully,
we are giving them important things, fourthly, but
give them proper solution. Friends,
whatever problem the customer has,
we have to narrow it down, we have to provide its solution,
if you feel
that the problem is of your level and you
can satisfy the customer, then you should
start it, if you feel that the
customer is not
hundred percent satisfied with your solution, then
you can transfer that call to your senior department,
both will contact the customer and
will start his problem and yes, all the
apps should also not make false comments to the customer, by making
false commitments to the customer, you
can keep the customer happy temporarily, but you cannot keep him
happy for a long time, you will
not be able to keep him as a customer of your company for a long time, so keep this thing in mind, just
before we have to disconnect the call, we should say some things  You have to say appreciative words to them
like have a nice day, have
a good day, you have given us important time,
thank you for taking out important time to talk to us and
we really enjoyed talking to you, so
you should say these things to the customer so that
a relationship can be maintained between the customer and us and the
customer calls our company again
and along with this, in
our entire process from the start of the call to the full pending,
you should keep in mind
that there should be a smile on your face,
everyone's communication skills should be good, the customer should
understand properly what you are saying
and you have to understand properly the questions asked by the customer, the
problems
he has, and you have to
talk to the customer politely, you should
not talk to the customer in an irritated manner,
so keep all these things in mind, so that's all
for now in this video, if you are
new to our YouTube channel, then subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon,
if you have any question related to the video,
then definitely let us know by commenting.  If you
liked the video then like it and
share it with your friends, see you
in the next video with a new topic, thank
you so much.